我们,是水晶
♪ We ♪ are the crystal
战士
♪ gems
我们总能拯救世界
♪ we'll always save the day
如果你认为我们不行
♪ and if you think we can't, ♪
我们总能找到方法
♪ we'll always find a way
这就是为什么这个世界
♪ that's why the people
的人
♪ of this world
相信
♪ believe in
石榴
♪ Garnet
紫晶
♪ Amethyst
和珍珠
♪ and Pearl
和史蒂文!
and Steven!
虎善士
欢迎关注微博@UUU字幕组，获取最新熟肉信息！
出品
UUU字幕组
翻译
FL1.2
校对
Husky
特效
presisco
压制
他们是你又爱又恨
They're the team you love to hate,
又恨又爱的团队
but also hate to love.
我爱摔角
I love wrestling!
紫色美洲狮和虎百万又使出了毁灭性的一击
Another devastating move by Purple Puma and Tiger Millionaire tonight, folks.
看来狂暴悍鲨经过这一重创也眼冒海星了
Looks like Shark-O-Mania's seeing starfish after that last one.
我们使出绝招来了结他吧
Let's finish him off with our special move.
哦 好啊
Yeah, why not?
抓住我的手
Take my hand.
向您呈现
Here it comes, y'all...
紫色百万
...the Purple Millionaire
之踢
Kick!
狂暴悍鲨昏过去了
And Shark-O-Mania's out cold.
快来人把那条鱼丢到冰块上 免得发臭了
Somebody put that fish on ice before it stinks up the joint.
朋友们 虎百万和紫色美洲狮再一次做到了
Folks, Tiger Millionaire and Purple Puma have done it again.
他们仍然是你们的双打联赛冠军
They are still your tag-team champions.
他们独家的丛林恐怖会有结束的一天吗
Will their special brand of jungle terror ever come to an end?
别啊 千万别结束
Yeah! Don't ever stop!
永远的虎百万和紫色美洲狮
Tiger Millionaire and Purple Puma forever!
真是团队合作和友情的最好的代名词
Such dedication to teamwork and friendship.
什么
What?!
嘿
Hey.
这挺好玩的 但
It's been fun, but...
我玩够了
I'm over this.
怎 怎么回事
W-What's going on?
我洗手不干了
I'm through with this place.
还你腰带
Here's your belt back.
喂 那个麦克风很贵的诶
Hey, now. That mic is expensive.
你不能就这么
You can't just --
哦 不 你就打算这样一走了之了?
Oh, no. You're just gonna do that and leave?
抱歉各位
Sorry, everyone.
看来 已经结束了
I guess this is over.
再见 笑脸先生
Bye, Mr. Smiley.
真是难以置信的遗憾啊 各位
What an unbelievable shame, folks.
什么 这就完了?
What?! That's it?
你不能现在退出
You can't quit now.
一个伟大的双打团队的职业生涯就在这摔角擂台上
What a sad and anticlimactic end to one of the greatest tag-team careers
悲壮而急转直下地落下帷幕
to ever grace the squared circle.
周六晚上终于又空出来了
Got my Saturday nights back.
你刚才说的是认真的吗
Did you really mean what you said
你真的打算不再摔角了?
about being through with wrestling?
拜托 史蒂文
Come on, Steven.
你不觉得那比赛有点无聊吗
Wasn't that match kind of boring?
我们不再需要靠摔角来找乐子了 对不对
We don't need wrestling to have fun anymore, right?
对
Right.
就是嘛
Yeah.
我们回家找点吃的去
Let's go home and get some grub.
嘿莎蒂 嘿拉尔斯
Hey, Sadie. Hey, Lars.
我能要特殊的吗
Can I get the special?
老虎
Tiger.
他在职业生涯的黄金时期放弃了摔角
He left wrestling at the height of his career.
为什么
Why-y-y-y?
你怎么不问问史蒂文呢
Why don't you just ask Steven?
那是你的想法
You and your theory.
史蒂文才不是老虎
Steven is not Tiger.
老虎肌肉发达 看上去有七英尺高
Tiger's ripped and like seven feet tall.
嗯 我听说紫色美洲狮不想再干了
Well, I heard Purple Puma didn't want to do it anymore.
又怎样
So what?!
紫色美洲狮不干又不代表虎也要跟着放弃
Just because Purple Puma quit doesn't mean Tiger had to.
我还听说虎没想到这一点
I also heard Tiger didn't think of that.
那他应该想到的
Well, he should have.
毕竟他也只能这样回馈粉丝了
It's the least he could do for his fans.
就是他没错吧
It is him, right?
我知道近段日子这里有些萧条
Now, I know these days, we're in a depression,
但地下摔角是不会因此而落寞的
but underground wrestling is too big to fail.
我们贷款调来了两名新战士
We've got two new fighters on loan,
而他们是来筹集资金的
and they're here to collect.
女士们先生们
Ladies and gentlemen,
有请华尔街之狼
the Wolves of Wall Street.
我们会愤怒 我们会咆哮 我们还会套牢你的股票
We'll huff, we'll puff, and we'll blow your stocks down.
真是山寨
What a rip-off.
谁来了
What's this?
看来我们有一个新的挑战者刚登上了擂台
It looks like we have a new challenger making his way into the ring.
在那隐藏身份的披风下究竟是何方神圣
What mystery could possibly lie beneath that identity-concealing shawl?
真不敢相信
I don't believe it.
是虎百万 女士们先生们
Tiger Millionaire, ladies and gentlemen!
你错了 笑脸先生
You're wrong, Mr. Smiley.
虎百万 已经不复存在了
Tiger Millionaire is gone forever.
他拿着一大笔钱退休了
He retired to his huge pile of money.
但他意识到这并不能使他快乐
But he realized it didn't make him happy,
于是我来到这里 准备好回馈粉丝
so here I am, ready to give back to the fans.
虎善士
Tiger Philanthropist!
所以百万富翁变成了一个慈善家
So, the millionaire becomes a philanthropist --
一个四处撒钱的人
a person who gives money away.
但我问你
But I ask you,
紫色美洲狮的小跟班能自己单打独斗么
can the Purple Puma's back-up make it solo?
等着瞧
Bring it on!
嘿 小硬汉
Hey, tough boy.
你需要贷款来做笔小生意吗
You need a loan to start a small business?
哦 我的经济收入其实很稳定的
Oh, I'm actually pretty financially stable.
因为你刚刚通过了审批
'Cause you've just been approved.
但我说了
But I just said --
我的天呐
Oh, my dang.
比利银行资产刚尝了一记善士商业贷款之肘击
Billy Bank Assets just got a taste of the Philanthropist business-loan elbow.
但是哈尔琼斯还在赛场上
Howl Jones is still in this match, though.
他想要取款
He's gonna make a withdrawal.
资金透支
Overdraft.
这些应该够付你们的医药费了
This should cover your medical bills.
多么慷慨的摔角手
What a generous wrestler.
哦 怎么
Oh, what?
看来狂暴悍鲨回来报仇了
Looks like Shark-O-Mania is back for revenge
还带来了个新搭档
with a new partner --
海黄毒蜂
the Sea Wasp,
海黄毒蜂, 澳洲箱水母的绰号
一种带有剧毒的水母
which is a very poisonous type of jellyfish.
看来我们得让他们尝尝紫色美洲...
Looks like we'll have to give 'em the ol' Purple Pu--
天呐 老虎将如何搞定这个充满鱼腥味的状况
Man, how's Tiger gonna get out of this fishy situation?
他使出了一记慈善捐款重击
He hit them with a charitable take-donation.
现在是商业投机弹射
And now a venture catapult-ist.
看到了吗
Did you see that?
他又付了医药费
He's paying for their medical bills, too.
看来这个慈善家是实打实的 女士们先生们
It looks like this philanthropist is the real deal, ladies and gentlemen.
今晚在座的每一位无不为之动容
No one is leaving here tonight unimpressed.
嗨 拉尔斯
Hi, Lars.
咋了
What?
说来
So...
你昨晚过得怎样
How was your evening?
还行吧
Fine, I guess.
有点无聊
Kind of boring.
你说有点无聊是什么意思
What do you mean kind of boring?!
你这么关心我晚上过得怎样是几个意思
Why are you so worked up over how my night was?
因为我在想你最近有没有看到什么
well, I was wondering if you'd seen any good
精彩的摔角比赛
wrestling matches lately.
既然你提到了
Now that you mention it,
没有
no.
但我听说虎百万回来了
But I heard Tiger Millionaire was back.
你最喜欢他了不是吗
He's your favorite, right?
没错 他是回来了 但却搞些蹩脚的
Yeah, but he came back as some lame
慈善机构之类的东西
Tiger Philharmonic donations thing,
讲真 搞得有点莫名其妙的 懂吗
which, honestly, is such a weird angle, you know?
整件事都感觉挺奇怪的
The whole thing just felt so off.
你说奇怪是什么意思
What do you mean off?
他脱下领带 还把钱到处撒
He took off his tie, and he's throwing money at everybody?
就像是
It's like
出了个没人想要的续集
the sequel no one asked for.
什么 这可是你想要的续集啊
What? It's the sequel you asked for.
怎么说 他就是看着不太走心 你懂
Well, he just didn't seem into it, you know?
他以前很在意他的钱的
He used to care about his money.
现在却四处乱散
Now he's just giving it away.
而且他还是那样 每场都赢
And he still just wins, like, every match.
哦 我懂了
Oh, I get it.
你想让他输 而且省着点花钱 对吧
You want him to lose and keep his money, right?
不 我不想让他输 只是
No, I don't want him to lose, just --
你想让他做什么
What do you want him to do?!
告诉我
Just tell me!
我不知道
I don't know!
我经常连早餐想吃啥都不知道
I don't even know what I want for breakfast half the time.
我是个复杂又独特的青春期少年
I'm a complex individual teenage boy.
现在给我出去
Now get out of here
别再对我幸福感和生活状况过度投资了
and stop taking such a personal interest in my happiness and well-being!
我不明白
I don't get it.
我都不知道我为什么还在摔角
I don't even know why I'm wrestling anymore.
我猜我是为了拉尔斯
I guess I'm doing it for Lars,
但他压根都不在乎
and he doesn't even care.
我更喜欢为了你做这些的时候
I liked it better when I was doing it for you.
但是谁稀罕呢 是吧
But who needs it, you know?
我是说 我以前需要它是因为
I mean, I needed it when I felt like...
我觉得自己不够好
I wasn't good enough.
但我不会再那样了
But I-I don't feel like that anymore.
你会吗
Do you?
不
No.
不 那 那从来不是我摔角的原因
No, that -- that's never why I was doing it.
我就是喜欢跟你一起做些什么的感觉
I just liked that it was our thing we did together.
但你是对的 这已经没什么意义了
But you're right. It doesn't make sense anymore.
我觉得我应该像你一样
I think I should just do what you did --
告诉大家我不干了 然后
just tell everybody I'm quitting and
毫不在乎地离开
leave like it's no big deal.
女士们先生们
Ladies and gents,
这是一个特别的夜晚
tonight is a very special night
就在这海滩市摔角竞技场的现场
here at the Beach City Wrestling Arena Dome and Building.
我会让我的好朋友虎百...
I'll let my good friend Tiger Mill--
我是说 善士 来解释
I mean, Philanthropist explain.
谢谢 笑脸先生
Thank you, Mr. Smiley.
又闹哪出
What now?
今晚将标志着我最伟大和最终的慈善行为
Tonight will mark my greatest and finalest act of philanthropy.
今晚 我会交出我联赛冠军的头衔
Tonight, I am giving away the tag-team titles.
谁先拿到 就归谁
Whoever can grab them first can have them.
切 慈善什么的弱爆了
Boo! Philanthropy is lame!
随你们怎么想 我已经无所谓了
Boo all you like. I don't care anymore.
这些腰带对我来说毫无意义
These belts don't mean anything to me.
从来如此
They never did.
我知道这声音
I know that sound.
是好哥们施工队
It's the Brothers Construction --
炽烈水泥和巨肌重卡
Concrete Heat and Chunk Truck.
真遗憾老虎就这么放弃了腰带
So sad to see Tiger giving up those belts
居然连一场战斗都没展开
without at least putting up a fight.
是帅爆徒的出场音乐
It's the Good-Looking Guys' music.
他们是回来夺取最后的头衔的
They're back to finally claim the tag titles.
看来擂台上正在预热
Looks like things are heating up in the ring.
谁会是下一届的双打联赛冠军
Who will be the next tag-team champion?!
你好啊 老虎
Whoa, there, Tiger.
紫晶
Amethyst?
他回来了
He's back!
传说已然重返擂台
The legend has returned to the ring!
紫色美洲狮
Pu-u-u-rple Pu-u-u-ma!
你不能就这么把腰带拱手相让
Those belts aren't yours to give away.
我们一起摔角的那些日子对我来说意味着一切
Those times we wrestled together meant everything to me.
你可以把那些丛林币通通送掉
You can give away all the jungle bucks you want,
但我不能眼睁睁看着你丢掉我们的回忆
but I will not stand by and let you give up our memories.
多么让人感动 女士们先生们
What a display, ladies and gentlemen.
你回来了
You came back.
对不起
I'm sorry.
这是我们一起做的事情 而我
This was our thing we did together, and
却抛下了你
I just quit on you.
没关系
It's okay.
你是对的 我们再也不需要这个了
You were right. We don't need this anymore.
那么 你想怎么退出呢
Well, then how do you want to go out?
轰轰烈烈地
With a bang.
看来腰带之争的战斗仍在继续
It looks like this fight for the belt is still on.
好哥们施工队看样子正准备打下一个痛苦的地基
The Brothers Construction look like they're ready to lay down a foundation of pain.
然而
But, oh.
狂暴悍鲨再度回到赛场
Shark-O-Mania is back again.
他甚至都不是比赛选手
He's not even in the match.
虎善士倒下了
Tiger Philanthropist is down.
什么
What?!
这不公平 快停止比赛
This isn't fair. Stop the match.
他们会被摧毁的
They're gonna be destroyed.
做个了断
Finish it.
不
No!
帅爆帮用苦命恋人击倒了美洲狮和老虎
The Good-Looking Gang hit the star-crossed lovers on Puma and Tiger.
他们的机会来了
This is their chance.
腰带就赤裸裸地挂在那儿
The belts are hanging free and clear.
他们拿到了 官方认证
They've got it. It's official.
帅爆帮是新一届海滩市
The Good-Looking Gang are the new Beach City
地下双打摔角联赛的冠军
Underground Tag-Team Wrestling Champions.
虎百万和紫色美洲狮的时代真的要告一段落了
This is truly the end for Tiger Millionaire and Purple Puma.
多么完美的谢幕
What a way to go out.
怎么会变成这样
How can this be happening?!
这正是上升期的时候
It was just getting good!
你不能现在放弃
You can't quit now!
老虎
Tiger!